{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.8.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":11628,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":28,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Title_AutoShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_2","title":"Interactive Module in IST 524 Instructional Technology Course ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_2","title":"Problems and Barriers of Integrating Technology into K-12 Classrooms    ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"Houda Bou Rafeh CSUMB Instructional Designer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si12848","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si12862","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide7903","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_1","Image_1","Button_1","si12848","si12862"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":603},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7903"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"Recognize the benefits of integrating technology in education  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"State solutions for the problems faced in k-12 technology integration  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si14289","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si14316","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_60","title":"Learning Objectives ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","title":"Describe the problems and barriers faced in k-12 technology integration  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide14172","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_3","Button_2","si14289","si14316","Text_Caption_60","Text_Caption_63"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":663},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide14172"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"Technology Integration ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_3","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"interactionId":"14353","quizId":-1,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"Throughout the 21st century, technology integration has reshaped our educational systems.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"“Technology is now considered by most educators and parents to be an integral part of providing a high-quality education” (U.S. DOE, 2003, as cited in Ertmer, 2005).   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_3","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si14451","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si14478","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si14544","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si14571","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide14317","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_5","Image_3","Image_4","Text_Caption_6","Text_Caption_7","Button_3","si14451","si14478","Button_4","si14544","si14571"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":516},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide14317"}}},{"id":"si20972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True/False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20979","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Technology integration is considered an integral part of providing a high-quality education and reshaping our educational systems. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20994","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20998","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20994_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21005","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21009","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21005_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21039","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20942q0","for":"Slide20942q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21056","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20942q0","for":"Slide20942q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21069","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20942q0","for":"Slide20942q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21013","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20942q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21419","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20942q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21432","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20942q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20942","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si20972","si20979","si20998","si21009","si21039","si21056","si21069","si21013"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20942"},"question":{"interactionId":"20959","quizId":379,"title":"True/False","text":"Technology integration is considered an integral part of providing a high-quality education and reshaping our educational systems.\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"Image_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"Benefits of Integrating Technology in Education ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"Teachers and students both benefit from integrating technology into the curriculum.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"When teachers effectively integrate technology into subject areas, teachers grow into roles of adviser, content expert, and coach  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","title":"Prepares students for the real world  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_12","title":"Engages students and creates active learners  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_13","title":"Facilitates peer collaboration  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si14792","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si14819","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si14885","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si14912","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide14617","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_5","Text_Caption_8","Text_Caption_9","Text_Caption_10","Text_Caption_11","Text_Caption_12","Text_Caption_13","Button_5","si14792","si14819","Button_6","si14885","si14912"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":2172},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide14617"}}},{"id":"si23646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23653","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What are some benefits of technology integration? Select all that apply. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23668","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23672","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Students are prepared for real world. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23672","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23616q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23668_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Students are prepared for real world.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23679","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23683","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Creates passive learning ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23683","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23616q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23679_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Creates passive learning\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24244","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24248","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Facilitates peer collaboration ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24248","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23616q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si24244_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Facilitates peer collaboration\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23713","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23616q1","for":"Slide23616q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23730","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23616q1","for":"Slide23616q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23616q1","for":"Slide23616q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24252","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23616q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24274","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23616q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24287","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23616q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23616","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si23646","si23653","si23672","si23683","si24248","si23713","si23730","si23743","si24274"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23616"},"question":{"interactionId":"23633","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What are some benefits of technology integration?\rSelect all that apply.\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","C"]}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_14","title":"Barriers of Integrating Technology  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_15","title":"Even though the conditions for successful technology integration (easy access to technology, enhanced teacher training, and a favorable policy environment), high-level technology use remains shockingly low.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"The decision to integrate technology depends on the teachers and their pre-existing attitudes toward it.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15004","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15017","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15049","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15062","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_7","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"1) Teachers’ Own Beliefs and Attitudes Toward Technology  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide15078","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_14","Text_Caption_15","Text_Caption_17","Button_7","si15004","si15017","Button_8","si15049","si15062","Image_7","Text_Caption_20"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1173},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide15078"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"2) Lack of Resources ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"Includes hardware and software, internet access, insufficient time, and technical support  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"Limited budgets  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","title":"Insufficient time for aligning technology with the curriculum and its goals  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_25","title":"Lack of technical support to assist the teachers in utilizing new technologies  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15186","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15199","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15231","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15244","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_10","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide15260","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_21","Text_Caption_22","Text_Caption_23","Text_Caption_24","Text_Caption_25","Button_9","si15186","si15199","Button_10","si15231","si15244","Image_9","Image_10"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1719},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide15260"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"Teachers are being overwhelmed by all the new technological tools and are skeptical of their ability to succeed  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":"Their self-efficacy is declining as well as their technological practices, which is affecting the students’ achievements and diminishing the learning process.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15352","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15365","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15397","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15410","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","title":"3) Low Self-Efficacy ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_12","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_13","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide15442","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_28","Text_Caption_29","Button_11","si15352","si15365","Button_12","si15397","si15410","Text_Caption_30","Image_12","Image_13"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":735},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide15442"}}},{"id":"si24347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Matching ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24354","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Match the following. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24385","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24389","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Teachers’ own beliefs and attitudes  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24406","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24410","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Low self-efficacy ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24427","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24431","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Lack of resources ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24372","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24376","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si24395","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24399","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Lack of technical support to assist the teachers in utilizing new technologies ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24399ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Lack of technical support to assist the teachers in utilizing new technologies","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si24416","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24420","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The decision to integrate technology depends on the teachers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24420ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The decision to integrate technology depends on the teachers","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si24437","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24441","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Teachers are being overwhelmed by all the new technological tools and are skeptical of their ability to succeed ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24441ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Teachers are being overwhelmed by all the new technological tools and are skeptical of their ability to succeed","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si24459","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24300q2","for":"Slide24300q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24476","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24300q2","for":"Slide24300q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24300q2","for":"Slide24300q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24446","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24300q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24514","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24300q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24527","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24300q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24300","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si24347","si24354","si24399","si24420","si24441","si24459","si24476","si24489","si24446"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24300"},"question":{"interactionId":"24317","quizId":379,"title":"Matching","text":"Match the following.\r","type":"knowledgeCheck","ikc":true,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[]}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"Strategic technology integration plan for how teachers are going to use technology to teach their students   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","title":"Continuous training for teachers to help them become more familiar with using technology  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_13","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15530","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15543","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_14","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15575","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15588","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"Teachers should learn about technology through professional development in the form of master's courses and accredited classes for in-service teachers, offers teachers the chance to learn from practitioners and experts currently using the technology ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_61","title":"Solutions ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide15632","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_31","Text_Caption_32","Button_13","si15530","si15543","Button_14","si15575","si15588","Text_Caption_34","Text_Caption_61"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1941},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide15632"}}},{"id":"si24570","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True/False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24577","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"One of the solutions suggested for the problems faced in K-12 technology integration is the continuous training for teachers to help them become more familiar with using technology.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24592","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24596","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24592_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24603","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24607","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24603_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24637","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24540q3","for":"Slide24540q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24654","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24540q3","for":"Slide24540q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24667","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24540q3","for":"Slide24540q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24611","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24540q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24681","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24540q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24694","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24540q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24540","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si24570","si24577","si24596","si24607","si24637","si24654","si24667","si24611"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24540"},"question":{"interactionId":"24557","quizId":379,"title":"True/False","text":"One of the solutions suggested for the problems faced in K-12 technology integration is the continuous training for teachers to help them become more familiar with using technology.\r\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"Let’s check how much you have learned  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"To review the content, click on the “ Back ” button ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_15","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15922","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15935","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_16","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15967","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15980","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"To start the assessment, click on the “ Take the Quiz “ button ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"Quiz ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16012","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_35","Text_Caption_36","Button_15","si15922","si15935","Button_16","si15967","si15980","Text_Caption_37","Text_Caption_38"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":396},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16012"}}},{"id":"si16301","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16297","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16217","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True/False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16224","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Technology is now considered by most educators and parents to be a peripheral part of providing a high-quality education. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16239","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16243","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16239_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16250","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16254","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16250_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16389","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16187q4","for":"Slide16187q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16406","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16187q4","for":"Slide16187q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16419","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16187q4","for":"Slide16187q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16258","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16187q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16271","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16187q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16187q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16187","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16217","si16224","si16243","si16254","si16389","si16406","si16419","si16284"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16187"},"question":{"interactionId":"16204","quizId":379,"title":"True/False\r","text":"Technology is now considered by most educators and parents to be a peripheral part of providing a high-quality education.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si16545","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16541","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16461","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True/False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16468","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"When teachers effectively integrate technology into subject areas, teachers grow into roles of adviser, content expert, and coach. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16483","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16487","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16483_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16494","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16498","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16494_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16633","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16431q5","for":"Slide16431q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16650","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16431q5","for":"Slide16431q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16663","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16431q5","for":"Slide16431q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16431q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16515","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16431q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16528","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16431q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16431","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16461","si16468","si16487","si16498","si16633","si16650","si16663","si16528"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16431"},"question":{"interactionId":"16448","quizId":379,"title":"True/False\r","text":"When teachers effectively integrate technology into subject areas, teachers grow into roles of adviser, content expert, and coach.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si16789","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16785","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16705","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True/False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16712","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The lengthy wait for technical assistance will cause the technology implementation to be delayed. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16727","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16731","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16727_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16738","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16742","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16738_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16877","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16675q6","for":"Slide16675q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16894","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16675q6","for":"Slide16675q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16907","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16675q6","for":"Slide16675q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16746","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16675q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16759","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16675q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16772","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16675q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16675","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16705","si16712","si16731","si16742","si16877","si16894","si16907","si16772"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16675"},"question":{"interactionId":"16692","quizId":379,"title":"True/False\r","text":"The lengthy wait for technical assistance will cause the technology implementation to be delayed.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si17033","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17029","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16949","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True/False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16956","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Self-efficacy is a person’s belief in their ability to succeed in a particular situation. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16971","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16975","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16971_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16982","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16986","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16982_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16919q7","for":"Slide16919q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17138","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16919q7","for":"Slide16919q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17151","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16919q7","for":"Slide16919q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16990","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16919q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17003","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16919q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16919q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16919","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16949","si16956","si16975","si16986","si17121","si17138","si17151","si17016"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16919"},"question":{"interactionId":"16936","quizId":379,"title":"True/False\r","text":"Self-efficacy is a person’s belief in their ability to succeed in a particular situation.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si17434","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17430","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17350","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17357","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Benefits of integrating technology in education. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17364","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17372","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17376","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Prepares students for the real world  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17372_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Prepares students for the real world\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17383","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17387","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Engages students and creates active learners   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17383_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Engages students and creates active learners\r\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18547","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18551","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Both A) and B)   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18547_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Both A) and B)\r\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si17522","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17320q8","for":"Slide17320q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17539","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17320q8","for":"Slide17320q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17552","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17320q8","for":"Slide17320q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17391","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17320q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17404","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17320q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17417","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17320q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17320","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17350","si17357","si17376","si17387","si18551","si17522","si17539","si17552","si17417"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17320"},"question":{"interactionId":"17337","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"Benefits of integrating technology in education.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si18907","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18903","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Short Answer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18851","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"State a barrier affecting technology integration in k-12 classrooms. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18858","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18863sha","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"teacher's own beliefs"}}},{"id":"si18995","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18821q9","for":"Slide18821q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19012","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18821q9","for":"Slide18821q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19025","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18821q9","for":"Slide18821q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18864","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18821q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18877","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18821q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18890","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18821q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18821","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18844","si18851","si18995","si19012","si19025","si18890"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18821"},"question":{"interactionId":"18838","quizId":379,"title":"Short Answer\r","text":"State a barrier affecting technology integration in k-12 classrooms.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"long-fill-in","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["teacher's own beliefs","lack of resources ","low self-efficacy "],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si17678","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17674","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17594","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17601","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Teachers' ___________ and ___________ toward technology are the most significant barriers to its use in the classroom. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17616","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17620","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Self-efficacy and View  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17616_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Self-efficacy and View\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17627","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17631","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Beliefs and attitudes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17627_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Beliefs and attitudes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si18562","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18566","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Knowledge and Skills  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18562_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Knowledge and Skills\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17766","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17564q10","for":"Slide17564q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17783","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17564q10","for":"Slide17564q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17796","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17564q10","for":"Slide17564q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17635","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17564q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17648","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17564q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17661","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17564q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17564","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17594","si17601","si17620","si17631","si18566","si17766","si17783","si17796","si17661"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17564"},"question":{"interactionId":"17581","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"Teachers' ___________ and ___________ toward technology are the most significant barriers to its use in the classroom.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si17922","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17918","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17838","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17845","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Integrating technology enables ___________ and produces  ___________ participant in the learning process. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17860","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17864","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Progressive learning, passive  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17860_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Progressive learning, passive\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17871","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17875","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Unexamined learning, active  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17871_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Unexamined learning, active\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18577","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18581","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Self-directed learning, active  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18577_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Self-directed learning, active\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si18010","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17808q11","for":"Slide17808q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18027","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17808q11","for":"Slide17808q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18040","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17808q11","for":"Slide17808q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17879","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17808q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17808q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17905","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17808q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17808","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17838","si17845","si17864","si17875","si18581","si18010","si18027","si18040","si17905"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17808"},"question":{"interactionId":"17825","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"Integrating technology enables ___________ and produces  ___________ participant in the learning process.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si18166","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18162","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18082","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18089","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Technology facilitates ___________ where students can teach each other through ___________ and creative cooperation ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18104","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18108","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Peer Collaboration, tutoring  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18104_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Peer Collaboration, tutoring\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18115","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18119","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Cooperative learning, mentoring  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18115_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Cooperative learning, mentoring\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18592","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18596","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Self-paced learning, training  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18592_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Self-paced learning, training\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si18254","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18052q12","for":"Slide18052q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18271","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18052q12","for":"Slide18052q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18052q12","for":"Slide18052q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18123","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18052q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18136","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18052q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18149","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18052q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18052","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18082","si18089","si18108","si18119","si18596","si18254","si18271","si18284","si18149"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18052"},"question":{"interactionId":"18069","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"Technology facilitates ___________ where students can teach each other through ___________ and creative cooperation\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si18410","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18406","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18326","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18333","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Teachers’ low self efficacy affects the students’ ___________ and diminishing the learning process ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18348","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18352","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Achievements  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18348_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Achievements\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si18359","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18363","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Knowledge ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18359_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Knowledge\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18607","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18611","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Skills ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18607_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Skills\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18498","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18296q13","for":"Slide18296q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18515","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18296q13","for":"Slide18296q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18528","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18296q13","for":"Slide18296q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18367","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18296q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18380","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18296q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18393","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18296q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18296","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18326","si18333","si18352","si18363","si18611","si18498","si18515","si18528","si18393"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18296"},"question":{"interactionId":"18313","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"Teachers’ low self efficacy affects the students’ ___________ and diminishing the learning process\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si19227","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19223","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19085","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Matching ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19092","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Match column 1 with column 2. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19099","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19123","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19127","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Benefit ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19144","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19148","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Barrier ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19165","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19169","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Solution ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19133","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19137","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Lack of technical support  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19137ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Lack of technical support ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si19154","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19158","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Strategic technology integration plan  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19158ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Strategic technology integration plan ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si19175","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19179","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Learning is engaging  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19179ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Learning is engaging ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si19315","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide19038q14","for":"Slide19038q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19332","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide19038q14","for":"Slide19038q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19345","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide19038q14","for":"Slide19038q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19184","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19038q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19197","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19038q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19038q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19085","si19092","si19137","si19158","si19179","si19315","si19332","si19345","si19210"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19038"},"question":{"interactionId":"19055","quizId":379,"title":"Matching","text":"Match column 1 with column 2.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si27058","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si27054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si26974","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26981","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You are being interviewed for a teaching position in a school district and have been asked how technology can be a useful tool for students. Which of the following is the most accurate and complete answer you can give? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27000","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Students can use technology as a tool in order to replace the teacher, practice skills such as research, and play games ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26996_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Students can use technology as a tool in order to replace the teacher, practice skills such as research, and play games\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27007","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27011","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Students can use technology as a tool in order to make learning fun, access social media, and practice skills such as research ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27007_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Students can use technology as a tool in order to make learning fun, access social media, and practice skills such as research\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27197","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27201","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Students can use technology as a tool in order to learn new things, demonstrate knowledge and practice skills such as research.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27197_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Students can use technology as a tool in order to learn new things, demonstrate knowledge and practice skills such as research.\r\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si27146","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26944q15","for":"Slide26944q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27163","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26944q15","for":"Slide26944q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27176","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26944q15","for":"Slide26944q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27015","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide26944q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27028","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide26944q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27041","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide26944q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide26944","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si26974","si26981","si27000","si27011","si27201","si27146","si27163","si27176","si27041"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide26944"},"question":{"interactionId":"26961","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"You are being interviewed for a teaching position in a school district and have been asked how technology can be a useful tool for students. Which of the following is the most accurate and complete answer you can give?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"Drag and Drop. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Benefits of Technology Integration         ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"Barriers of Technology Integration         ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_19","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19746","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19773","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_50","title":"Peer collaboration   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_51","title":"Active learners  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","title":"Limited Budgets   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_22","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si22083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si22110","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_53","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_53","title":"Overwhelmed teachers by the new technological tools   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","title":"Reshaping the educational system  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_55","title":"Low self-efficacy  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_2","title":"Incorrect- Try Again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Interaction_4q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_2","title":"Correct- Great Job! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Interaction_4q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20201","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si20218","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si20231","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide19561","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_43","SmartShape_2","SmartShape_3","Button_19","si19746","si19773","Text_Caption_50","Text_Caption_51","Text_Caption_52","Button_22","si22083","si22110","Text_Caption_53","Text_Caption_54","Text_Caption_55","Failure_Shape_2","Success_Shape_2"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19561"},"dragDrop":{"sources":[19994,20004,20014,20024,20034,20044],"targets":[19581,19626],"question":"Interaction_4q16"}}},{"id":"si17188","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17196","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17204","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17212","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17220","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17228","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17177","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17184","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17192","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Maximum Score: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17200","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17208","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17216","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17224","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Attempts: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17232","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17236","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17253","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17266","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17278","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17295","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17163","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17163"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_3","title":"References ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_3","title":"https://www.chispahousing.org/community/attachment/csumb-logo/ Blackburn, S. (2019). The 11 barriers to technology adoption https://districtadministration.com/computer-technology-in-schools-barriers-to-technology-integration/ Christensen, D. (2019). What does “technology integration” mean? https://www.classcraft.com/blog/definition-of-technology-integration-in-education/ Ertmer, P. A. (2005). Teacher Pedagogical Beliefs: The Final Frontier in Our Quest for Technology Integration? Educational Technology Research and Development, Vol 53, No 4, pp. 25-39. https://fromcoachtoteacher.wordpress.com/issues-with-ict-in-teaching-lack-of-technical-support-or-knowlege/ Harris-Briggs, N. (2018). Ideas for using technology in the classroom.https://www.avocor.com/blog/ideas-for-using-technology-in-the-classroom/ Kim, B. (2013). How to solve the 10 most common tech support problems yourself https://www.pcworld.com/article/447413/how-to-solve-the-10-most-common-tech-support-problems-yourself.html Lopez-Garrido, G. (2020). Self-Efficacy Theory | Simply Psychology. Self-Efficacy Theory | Simply Psychology. https://www.simplypsychology.org/self-efficacy.html. Reiser, R. A., & Dempsey, J.V. (2017). Trends and Issues in Instructional Design and Technology. (4th edition) Pearson  https://talloiresnetwork.tufts.edu/california-state-university-monterey-bay-usa/ ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22423","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22423"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Final_Project","class":"project","title":"Final_Project","children":["Slide7903","Slide14172","Slide14317","Slide20942","Slide14617","Slide23616","Slide15078","Slide15260","Slide15442","Slide24300","Slide15632","Slide24540","Slide16012","Slide16187","Slide16431","Slide16675","Slide16919","Slide17320","Slide18821","Slide17564","Slide17808","Slide18052","Slide18296","Slide19038","Slide26944","Slide19561","Slide17163","Slide22423"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide20942q0","Slide23616q1","Slide24300q2","Slide24540q3","Slide16187q4","Slide16431q5","Slide16675q6","Slide16919q7","Slide17320q8","Slide18821q9","Slide17564q10","Slide17808q11","Slide18052q12","Slide18296q13","Slide19038q14","Slide26944q15","Interaction_4q16"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":130,"passScore":104}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"navigationEnabled":true,"navigateVisitedSlides":false,"collapseAll":false,"showTopicDuration":true,"statusFlag":true,"selfPaced":true,"showSearch":true,"enabled":true},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide26944","title":"Slide 25","visible":false},{"id":"Slide7903","title":"Beginning of Module","visible":true},{"id":"Slide14172","title":"Learning Objectives ","visible":true},{"id":"Slide14317","title":"Technology Integration","visible":true},{"id":"Slide20942","title":"Knowledge Check 1","visible":true},{"id":"Slide14617","title":"Benefits of Integrating Technology ","visible":true},{"id":"Slide23616","title":"Knowledge Check 2","visible":false},{"children":[{"id":"Slide15078","title":"Teacher's Own Beliefs and Attitudes Toward Technology ","visible":true},{"id":"Slide15260","title":"Lack of Resources","visible":true},{"id":"Slide15442","title":"Low Self-Efficacy","visible":true},{"id":"Slide24300","title":"Knowledge Check 3","visible":false}],"title":"Barriers of Integrating Technology","visible":true},{"id":"Slide15632","title":"Solutions","visible":true},{"id":"Slide24540","title":"Knowledge Check 4 ","visible":false},{"children":[{"id":"Slide16012","title":"Begin Quiz","visible":true},{"id":"Slide16187","title":"Quiz Question 1","visible":true},{"id":"Slide16431","title":"Quiz Question 2","visible":true},{"id":"Slide16675","title":"Quiz Question 3","visible":true},{"id":"Slide16919","title":"Quiz Question 4","visible":true},{"id":"Slide17320","title":"Quiz Question 5","visible":true},{"id":"Slide18821","title":"Quiz Question 6","visible":true},{"id":"Slide17564","title":"Quiz Question 7","visible":true},{"id":"Slide17808","title":"Quiz Question 8","visible":true},{"id":"Slide18052","title":"Quiz Question 9","visible":true},{"id":"Slide18296","title":"Quiz Question 10","visible":true},{"id":"Slide19038","title":"Quiz Question 11","visible":true},{"id":"Slide19561","title":"Quiz Question 12","visible":true}],"title":"Quiz","visible":true},{"id":"Slide22423","title":"References ","visible":true}]}